Guide to the Doris Duke American Indian oral history project audio recordings 1949-1972
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Elizabeth Howard, 1971 September 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1247)
  Cultural Center
  Interviewed and recorded by F. A. O'Neil and G. C. Thompson
- Steven Wall, 1971 September 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1248)
- Dean Randall Taylor, 1971 September 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1249)
- Arthur Ballantine, 1971 September 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1250)
- President Rexer Berndt, 1971 September 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1251)
- Stan Lyman, 1971 October 30; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1252)
  Interviewed and recorded by F. A. O'Neil and K. MacKay
- Recording unavailable (Reel 1253)
- Frank Boudinot, Jr., 1971 September 07; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1254)
  Interviewed and recorded by Helen Amgwerd in Long Beach, California
  Running Time: 1 hour
- Joe Seaboy, 1971 August 24; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1255)
  Interviewed and recorded by M. DeCarlo
  Running Time: 3 hrs
- Tommie Tsosie (Navajo), 1971 November 12; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1256)
  BIA Employment Issues
  Interviewed and recorded by K. MacKay
- Margaret A. Lewis (Zuni), 1971 April 17; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1257)
  7 reel-to-reel audiotapes
- James Monroe, 1971 October 19; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1258)
  Interviewed and recorded by Helen Amgwerd in Fullerton, California
  Running Time: 1 hour 15 min
- Frank Dudoint, 1971 May 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1259)
  Running Time: 2 hrs 15 min
- Recordings unavailable (Reel 1260-1269)
- Dr. Reed Baily, 1965 May 04; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1270)
  Interviewed and recorded by A. R. Standing
- Angela Ramirez, 1971 March 24; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1271)
  Interviewed and recorded by Nancy Callaci California
  Running Time: 54 min
- Jim Mike; Mel Smith, 1972; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1272)
  Tim Mike and the discovery of Rainbow Bridge.
  Interviewed and recorded by R. Hunt
- Jim Mike, 1972 May; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1273)
  Exploring Rainbow bridge area.
  Interviewed and recorded by J. Hammond
- Recordings unavailable (Reel 1274-1276)
- Yah Na Bah Winker, 1971 November 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1277)
  Ethnohistory Project
  5 reel-to-reel audiotapes
  Interviewed and recorded by D. Brugge and Roberta Tso
- Recordings unavailable (Reel 1278-1281)
- T'iss Yazhi, Yazzie Holmes, Joe Tippecanoe, 1971 November 09; 1971 November 16; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1282-1284)
  Interviewed and recorded by D. Brugge and R. Tso.
- Tom Morgan, Joe Tippecanoe, Hastiin Yellowhair, 1971 November 19; 1971 November 22; 1971 December 06; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1285-1287)
- Frank Tsosie (Navajo), 1971; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1288)
  Reel-to-reel audiotapes
- Arthur Hubbard Sr., 1971 December 01; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1289)
- Asdzaan Doo Holoni, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1290)
- Elsie Yazzie (Navajo), 1972 January 14; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1291)
- Mrs. Ben Wilson, 1972 January 17; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1292)
- Pete Hubbard Sr., 1972 January 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1293)
  Interviewed and recorded by D. Brugge.
- Marie H. Curley, 1972 January 24; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1294)
- Blacksheep, 1972 February 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1295)
- Tully Lincoln, 1972 February 01; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1296)
  Interviewed and recorded by R. Tso.
- Annie J. Hubbard, 1972 February; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1297)
- Hosteen Pete, 1972 February 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1298)
- Rafael Candlaria, 1972 February 18; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1299)
- Dlinibaa' Morgan, 1972 March 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1300)
- Joe Tippecanoe, 1972 April; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1301)
- Recording unavailable (Reel 1302)
- Tom Morgan, 1972 April 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1303)
- Marie Etsitty, 1972 April 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1304)
- Recordings unavailable (Reel 1305-1306)
- May Alice Hubbard, 1972 April; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1307)
  Interviewed and recorded by M. Hubbard.
- Recording unavailable (Reel 1308)
- T'iis Yazhi, 1972 April 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1309)
  Interviewed and recorded by M. Hubbard and D. Brugge.
- Recordings unavailable (Reel 1310-1311)
- John Kiiya'aanii, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1312)
- Recording unavailable (Reel 1313)
- Net Silvers, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1314)
- Recordings unavailable (Reel 1315-1316)
- Friday Kinichii'nii-House Blessing, 1972 May 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1317)
  Ethnohistory Project-House Blessing as part of establishment
- Recordings unavailable (Reel 1318-1321)
- Witnesses in Navajo-Hopi Land Disputes, 1960 September 01; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1322)
  Navajo-Hopi land disputes.
  Interviewed and recorded by A. Williams and W. Wolf
- Witnesses in Navajo-Hopi Land Disputes, 1960 September 01; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1323)
- Witnesses in Navajo-Hopi Land Disputes, 1960 September 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1324)
- Witnesses in Navajo-Hopi Land Disputes, 1960 September 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1325)
- Witnesses in Navajo-Hopi Land Disputes, 1960 September 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1326)
- Witnesses in Navajo-Hopi Land Disputes, 1960 September 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1327)
- Witnesses in Navajo-Hopi Land Disputes, 1960 September 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1328)
- Witnesses in Navajo-Hopi Land Disputes, 1960 September 06; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1329)
- Witnesses in Navajo-Hopi Land Disputes (Navajo), 1960 September 14; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1330)
  3 reel-to-reel audiotape
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1966 June 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1331)
  The story of a Priest's son.
  Interviewed and recorded by Zuni Tribe and Alvina Quam
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1966 June 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1332)
  Story of a Priests Son, story of an Orphan.
  Interviewed and recorded by Zuni Tribe and A. Quam
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1966 June 30; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1333)
  "The Pretty Girl Combs and Kills"
  Interviewed and recorded by the Zuni Tribe and a. Quam
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1966 July 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1334)
  "The Priests Son and the Land of The Virgins", "The Yellow Ant", "The Witches Ghost and The Priests Son".
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1966 July 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1335)
  "The Witches Ghost and The Priests Son", "The Girl Who Went to the Spirit World".
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1966 July 19; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1336)
  "The Squirrel and The Prairie Dog", "The Deer Hunter Girl", "The War Chief and the Door Woman".
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1966 August 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1337)
  "The War Chief and the Door Woman", "Story of Yellow House", "Story of Bak-who-chu".
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1966 August 19; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1338)
  "Story of Bak-who-chu", "Story of Gee-le-le", "Story of Ah-Dosh-le".
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1966 September 06; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1339)
  "Story of Ah-Dosh-Le", "A Priests Son", Kucate and the Navajos, "Zuni Runner and the Deer".
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1966 October 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1340)
  "Zuni Runner and the Deer", Story of The Hopi, "Story of Ha-Lo-Na-Wa", "Village of Hopi and Priests Daughter".
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1966 November 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1341)
  "Village of Hopi and Priests Daughter", "Story of Zuni Village", "The Rabbit and Jack Rabbit", "Story of Ka-Ki-Ma".
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1966 November 21; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1342)
  "Story of Ka-Ki-Ma", Kucate and his days of racing horses, "Priest Boy and the Girls", story of Zuni Village, Kucate's Childhood.
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1966 December 17; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1343)
  Kucate's Childhood, Zuni Shalako, Kucate's grandmother and his son, Life in Bin-na-wa, Story of Hawikuh, "The Priests son the Gambler".
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1967 January 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1344)
  "The Priest's son, the Gambler", Ah-Ha-Vada and their Grandmother, Two girls in Ha-Lo-Na-Wa.
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1967 January 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1345)
  Two girls in Ha-Lo-Na-Wa, "The Priests son", "Hopi Village and the Priests Daughter", Story about gambling, She-Ka-Boo.
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1967 February 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1346)
  She-Ka-Boo, Hopi Village, Ka-Kee-Ma Village.
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1967 March 07; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1347)
  Ka-Kee-Ma village, Kucate's traveling experiences, Three-eyed Sheepherder.
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1967 March 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1348)
  Three-eyed Sheepherder, Rabbits and Jack Rabbits, Ka-Kee-Ma Village and Priests Daughter, Art and Kucate's Navajo Girlfriend, Daniel and the Mexican Bar.
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1967 April 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1349)
  Story of the Ka-Kee-Ma, White Dancers, Black Dancers.
- Theodore Kucate (Zuni), 1967 April 18; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1350)
  White Dancers and Black Dancers, Story of Bel-Ollay-Mah, Kucate's Traveling and Dancing.
- Awashu (Zuni), 1967 January 16-April 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1351)
  Awashu's uncle in California, A-Ha-U-Da and the Navajo Girl, The Deer Hunter from Mah-Sah-Ka, The Hopi Priests son.
- Awashu (Zuni), 1967 January 16-April 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1352)
  The Hopi Priests Son, Deer Hunter of the Yellow House Village, Village of Kakima.
- Awashu (Zuni), 1967 January 16-April 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1353)
  Deer Hunter of Yellow House Village, Hopi Village Poor Boy, Ha-Lon-Ah Village and the Priests Son, the story of the Mountain Lion and the Deer.
- Awashu (Zuni), 1967 January 16-April 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1354)
  The story of Rainbow and Turkey Hunter, story of A-Ha-U-Da.
- Awashu (Zuni), 1967 January 16-April 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1355)
  Flight in Nutria, story about a man who killed a bear in Cliff Dwelling, famine in Zuni.
- Acque (Zuni), 1966 July-1967 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1356)
  Stories of: Ba-Ya-Da-Mo, Ah-Dosh-Le, Ka-Kee-Ma, The Pinion squirrel and The Antelope, the Coyote and the Bob Cat, War Gods and the Knife Society, War Gods and the Monster, Deer Hunting time, Thunderbird Capturing a Girl, Coyote and the Ba-Ya-Da-Mo, Depression time.
- Acque (Zuni), 1966 July-1967 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1357)
  Knockouts, Coyote Who got married to a Lion, Indian Maiden and her flock of Turkeys, Boy and grandmother who did not have any friends, Coming of the Spaniards, Tornado and the Bumble Bee, What we were told by our old folks, finding the center of the Earth, Navajos went out to make slaves, story about Ah-Dosh-Le.
- Acque (Zuni), 1966 July-1967 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1358)
  Stories of: A-Dosh-Le, Coyote and the Badger, Badger and the Porcupine, Zunis and the Apaches, Coyote and the Birds, Den-A-Tse-Le, Salt Mine near Black Rock, Ka-Na-Qua, Ba-Ya-Da-Mo.
- Acque (Zuni), 1966 July-1967 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1359)
  Stories of: Ah-Yah-Ho-Que, an earthquake, The Priests Son, Zunis and THe Apaches, Ka-Ke-Ma, The Bob Cat and The Coyote, two girls who lived in Ka-Ke-Ma, and Ashowna.
  Interviewed and recorded by The Zuni Tribe and A. Quam.
- Acque (Zuni), 1966 July-1967 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1360)
  Stories of: Depression Times, The Girl Rabbit Hunter, The Man Who Ran Against the Sun, Acqe's Team of Oxen, The Seeko and the Bull Snake, The Bear and the Priests Son, Mah-Sah-Ka, The Spanish Woman Who Sold Her Baby to a Fish For Gold, The Poor Mexican Boy, War between Zunis and Navajo, and The Origination of the Moon.
- Acque (Zuni), 1966 July-1967 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1361)
  Stories of: The Origination of The Moon, A Snake Girl, A Hopi Village, The Coyote and Ah-Ha-u-Da, An Outlaw, The Original names of places, The Racer (The Priests Son), The Priests Daughter, A Mountain Village.
- Acque (Zuni), 1966 July-1967 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1362)
  Stories of: A Mountain Village, The Gambler, Aque's Boyhood, Cochite and the Ugly Creature, The Deer Hunter and The Priests Son, The Creation, Ah-ho-U-The, an Earthquake in The Hopi Village, The Apache War and Zunis, Eastern Pueblo Country, Ha-Lo-No-War, and The Sun's Son.
- Acque (Zuni), 1966 July-1967 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1363)
  Stories of: The Sun's Son, Ka-Ke-Mah Village, The Creation of Zuni and Laguna's, White Shoo-Mas-Coolie, A Zuni Village, The Zuni Dancer, Zuni and Hopi Singers, the Zuni Witch, and The Creation of Zuni.
- Acque (Zuni), 1966 July-1967 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1364)
  Stories of: The Creation of Zuni, Zuni Dancer and THe Priests Daughter, An Earthquake, She-Kah-Bo, The Coyote and The Bob Cat.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1365)
  Stories of: The Zunis and Apaches, The Zunis and The Navajos, The Sun Priest's Son, Two Brothers, The Son of The Rain Priest.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1366)
  The story of The Son of The Rain Priest.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1367)
  Stories of: Zunis and the Outlaws, Bear and Rabbit Race, Growing Up, a Navajo story, Two Sons of A Priest.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1368)
  Stories of: Two Sons of A Priest, and The Deer Hunter and The Cotton Boys.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1369)
  Stories of: The Deer Hunter and The Cotton Boys, and The Dance Leader's Daughter
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1370)
  Continuation of the story of The Dance Leaders Daughter.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1371)
  Stories of: The War God's Daughter, Zuni Runner, and The Dragon Fly and the Famine.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1372)
  Stories of: The Dragon Fly and the Famine, The Girl farmer and the Oriole, The Lazy Porcupine and the Man Badger, and The Sun's Creation of A Navajo.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1373)
  Stories of: The Priests Son and the Spirit World, and The Lonkeena and the Horse Thieves.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1374)
  Stories of: The Lonkeena and the Horse Thieves, The Search for the Stu-Di-Kyn's Medicine, The Return of The Zuni Slave Woman, Hanging of The Zuni Witches, The Coyote and The Badger, and Navajos and the She-She's Wife.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1375)
  Stories of: The Navajos and the She-She's Wife, The Outcast Boy and the Priests Daughters, Zunis and the Navajos, and The Story of Doo-Be.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1376)
  Stories of: Doo-Be, Zuni Slave and The Navajos, The Poor Woman and Flower Girl, Qua-Keen-Aah, The Sun Priest's Daughter, and The Ah-Dash-La.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1377)
  Stories of: Ah-Dash-La, Zuni Slave of the Navajos, The Priest's Daughter and The Owl, She-Ka-Boo and the Apaches, and The Sun's Son and The Deer.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1378)
  Stories of: The Sun's Son and The Deer, Zunis and The Navajos, The Blackbirds and the Coyote, Ah-Ha-U-Da and Their Grandmother, Ho-Quee-Sho and The Navajos, The Priest's Son, Who-Son-Doe-Hir The Hunter, The Zuni Ghost Dance, and Hanging Skin and the Snake.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1379)
  Stories of: Hanging Skin and The Snake, The Turkey, Zuni and The Navajos, The Was Gods and The Priest's Son, I-Who-Lee and The Eagles, and The Priest's Son and the Earthquake.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1380)
  Stories of: The Priest's Son and the Earthquake, Quan-lu-bee the Warrior, Zuni Runners and The Snake, The Priest Who Never Walked Out of the House, War between Zunis and The Apaches, War Between Navajo and The Zunis, The Navajo Albino and Zunis, Zuni Races, Race Between the Horse and the Deer, Kai-nee-que, and Cactus Fruit of the Bear.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1381)
  Stories of: Cactus Fruit of The Bear, The Salt Woman, Tsi-Ah-She and The Navajos, Lonkeena in a Stick Race, War Gods, The Sparrow and The Priest's Daughter in Lonely Village, The Famine Village of Ka-Ke-Ma, Apaches Attack on Two Old Men, Lonkeena's Hunting Trips, Fight Between Navajos and The Zunis, How The High Priest Caused Famine.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1382)
  Stories of: How The High Priest Caused Famine, Little Arrowheads, Navajo Warrior, Chu-Ma-Lee and Coyote, The Priest's Daughter's Revenge, The Priest's Son in Kawiah, The Girl Thief, Rabbit Hunter From Lonely Village, Little Boy and The Antelopes, Ah-Ha-U-Da and The Girl in Ka-Kee-ma, and Navajos and Zunis.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1383)
  Stories of: The Priest and his Son From Cotton Fields, The Man From Ka-Ne-Ga Village, Navajos and Zunis, Village of Mat-Sah-Kya,A Brave Boy and the Ugly Creature, Navajo Sheep, Hopi Village, The Story of Grandfather, and Old Grandfather and War.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1384)
  Stories of: Old Grandfathers Hunting, Zunis in California, Why The Salt Woman Left Black Rock, Customs of Hopi Marriage, Raising of Plants in Hopi Village, and Bear Hunting in We-Ma-Ya- Cave.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1385)
  Stories of: Bear Hunting in We-Ma-Ya Cave, Ed Vanderwagen and The Bears, Hopi Village, Hopi Ghost, Wa-La-Lupe and Wa-Lupe, The Mexican, and She-Ka-Bo.
- Lonkeena (Zuni), 1966 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1386)
  Stories of: She-Ka-Bo, Revenge Against The Apaches, San Domingo's Religious Dancers Search For a New Home, The Navajo Warrior Kelth-Na-Kya, How The Hopis Manke Prayer Sticks, and Doo-Who-Li.
- Tom Awelagate (Zuni), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1387)
  Stories of: The Buffalo, The Snake, The Coyote and The Crow, and Ah-Dosh-La.
- Tom Awelagate (Zuni), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1388)
  Stories of: Ah-Dosh-La, The Stick Race, The Fox and The Woodpecker, The Coyote and The Kai-Na-Qua, and The Ghost and The Girl.
- Tom Awelagate (Zuni), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1389)
  Stories of: The Ghost and The Girl, The Fox and The Grandmother, The Priest's Son and His Mother, War Gods and The Blue Horns (The Origination of Initiation), and The Indian Maiden Who Was a Farmer.
- Tom Awelagate (Zuni), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1390)
  Stories of: The Indian Maiden Who Was a Farmer, The Oriole and The Winter, Coyote and The Crow, and The Indian maiden Who Wanted to marry a War God.
- Tom Awelagate (Zuni), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1391)
  The story of "Yellow Coyote" The Caciques Son.
- Tom Awelagate (Zuni), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1392)
  Stories of: "Yellow Coyote" The Cocique's Son, Hopi Deer Hunter and The Witch's Ghost, The Bear on Towa Yallane and The Pinion Peckers, and the story of Socorro.
- Tom Awelagate (Zuni), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1393)
  Stories of: The Socorro, Ka-Ke-Ma, and The Boy and The Giant.
- Tom Awelagate (Zuni), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1394)
  Stories of: The Boy and The Giant, The Priest's Daughter and The Prairie Dog, The Cacique and The Ghost, The Hopi Corn Planter, Jackrabbit and The Rabbit, and The Twins With Gold and Silver Hair.
- Tom Awelagate (Zuni), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1395)
  Stories of: The Twins With Gold and Silver Hair, The King From The West and The King From The East, Hawikuh and Ka-Chee-By-Wa, The Creation of Santa Nina, Zuni Predictions, Origin of The Fraternal Coyote Society, Zunis at Towa Yallane, Tom Awelagate's Boyhood, How The Zunis Lives, The Ghost and The Deer Hunter, and the story of The Gambler.
- Tom Awelagate (Zuni), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1396)
  Stories of: The Butterfly, and The Deer hunter.
- Tom Awelagate (Zuni), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1397)
  Stories of: The Coyote, THe Deer Hunter, and The Coyote and The Badger.
- Tom Awelagate (Zuni), 1996; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1398)
  Stories of: The Zuni Village, The War God, and Coyote and His Grandmother.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1399)
  Stories of: The Coyote and The Doe, Apaches and Zunis, and The Buffalo.
  2 reel-to-reel audiotape
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1400)
  Stories of: Oriole and His Grandmother, The Hog, and a story of The Hopis.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1401)
  Stories of: Salentonio and Ne-Nio, and Cha-Bah-Yo-Day and his Grandmother.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1402)
  Stories of: Cha-Bah-Yo-Day and his Grandmother, and of Tom Luna's Boyhood.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1403)
  Stories of: The Hopis, and Mah-Sah-Ka.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1404)
  Stories of: Mah-Sah-Ka, and of Hontlebinka.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1405)
  Story of Hontlebinka.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1406)
  Story of Hontlebinka, and The Salt Mother.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1407)
  Stories of: The Salt Mother, and The Trip to the Setting Sun.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1408)
  The story of The Trip to the Setting Sun.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1409)
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1410)
  Stories of: The Trip to the Setting Sun, and The Roman Luna.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1411)
  Stories of: The Roman Luna and Catle-Nut-Da, and of Boo-Whosh-Ki-She.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1412)
  Stories of: Boo-Whosh-Ki-She, and The Fox and The Badger Go For Salt.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1413)
  Stories of: The Fox and The Badger Go For Salt, and The Priest's Daughter.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1414)
  The story of The Cactus Girls.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1415)
  The Story of The Cactus Girls.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1416)
  Stories of: The Cactus Girls, and The Creation.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1417)
  The story of Creation.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1418)
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1419)
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1420)
  Stories of: Ants in Ha-Lo-na Village, A Great Land Slide, and The Poor Boy From Mexico.
- Tom Luna (Navajo), 1966; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1421)
  The story of Du-Woe-Cio.
- Massie (Zuni), 1966-1967; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1422)
  Stories of: She-Stu-Kai, The Girls Who Wanted Pottery, and The Origin of The Hopi Snake Society.
- Massie (Zuni), 1966-1967; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1423)
  Stories of: The Priest's Daughter To Be Married, Hay-Sho-Tah, and The Deer Hunter.
- Massie (Zuni), 1966-1967; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1424)
  Stories of: The Deer Hunter, The Hopi Land, and Two Boys and Their Grandmother Who Never Had Friends.
- Massie (Zuni), 1966-1967; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1425)
  Stories of: The Two Boys and Their Grandmother Who Never Had Friends, The Mountain Lion Meets Two Witch Girls, and The Boy Who Was Raised By A Mother Deer.
- Massie (Zuni), 1966-1967; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1426)
  Stories of: The Boy Who Was Raised By A mother Deer, Depression Times, and The Priest's Daughter and The Serpent.
- Massie (Zuni), 1966-1967; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1427)